The kettle and the idol
So, secondly, you have no friends?
Yes, I have no friends.
What do you mean by that?
Well, I'm...
I'm quite shy.
I've always said I wanted to have friends.
I've been saying that I want to have friends.
But...
I realized I had no one.
That's not true.
Someone who spends his life smiling at you...
If there's no one around when you realize that... You can't do that.
It's not true, but I'm the type of person who thinks about it a lot.
So when I ask someone out, I wonder if it's okay for me to say this or if they won't like it, so I can't ask them out.
This is not really any advice, but...
To be honest, I don't really think that much about it.
That's right.
Think about it yourself.
But do you think that much about other people?
Not at all.
Not at all, right?
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
That's not enough.
No, because if I was approached by such a cute girl...
Everyone would go out with her.
I don't have a schedule, that's all.
But what do you usually do?
My private life is very private.
I know you don't like to reveal too much.
Not really.
Not really?
But I often go to see the cherry blossoms by myself.
What?
I go to hot springs alone.
I do that after all.
I guess so.
By yourself?
I've been an idol for a long time.
I haven't participated in many events.
I didn't have much fun on weekends.
I'm not very good at socializing.
I'm not good at socializing.
I have to think of this as a little bit of an office problem in our
entertainment.
Our lives.
You know, people who put their lives on the line to bring smiles to people's faces...
I haven't been able to participate in a lot of events.
It's going to be difficult for a month.
Well, now that you mention it...
But it's okay, because I have the members.
That's why I love Mr. Tork the most
I want to be with him all my life.
What about the members? Stay with me.
Members?
They're all very kind.
They're all kind.
Kind-hearted... from the countryside.
But it's kind of at night.
It's a nighttime title.
Mew said she probably doesn't have any friends.
She said that.
Yeah... some kind of déjà vu.
Really? I thought we were looking at the same scenery, but then he said he had no friends. Oh, he did! Oh, yeah! Yeah! It was some kind of déjà vu. Really?
I thought I was seeing the same thing.
How about someone who doesn't have any friends?
I don't have any friends.
So when I see them, it's great.
We talk about going out together.
Oops.
We just talk.
We do talk.
That's nice.
You don't like rain?
But I have feelings... and I have feelings... for how many years?
How many years has it been since you've had feelings for me?
Seven years.
Seven years and you've never gone.
Yes.
That's what you're saying, isn't it?I guess that's what I'm saying.
We both sound superficial.
I'm sorry, does it sound superficial?
Not at all.
We're both speaking in superlatives.
We're talking over each other.
This show...
Karen's Marilyn.
Koji-san.
Ms. Tsukasa
Iginari DD Keisuke-san and Pajamas-san provided the entertainment!
Thank you for always being there for me.
Your smile is the best in the world